http://www.amte.net/amte-privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Show/Hide Sidebar
AMTE Privacy Policy
Your privacy is critically important to us. At AMTE we have a few fundamental principles:
We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law or develop our services.
We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of our services.
We aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.
Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:
If you have questions about deleting or correcting your personal data please contact our support team.
The Association of Mathematics Teacher Educators ("AMTE") operates several websites, including amte.net and starfellows.com. It is AMTE's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.
Website Visitors
Like most website operators, AMTE collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. AMTE's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how AMTE's visitors use its website. From time to time, AMTE may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.
AMTE also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses for logged in users and for users leaving comments. AMTE only discloses logged in user and commenter IP addresses under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information as described below, except that commenter IP addresses and email addresses are visible and disclosed to the administrators of the page where the comment was left.
Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information
Certain visitors to AMTE's websites choose to interact with AMTE in ways that require AMTE to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that AMTE gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with AMTE – by purchasing a membership for example - are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, AMTE collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with AMTE. With the exception of professional directory information, AMTE does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.
Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information
AMTE discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on AMTE's behalf or to provide services available at AMTE websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using AMTE's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. AMTE will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, AMTE discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when AMTE believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of AMTE , third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an AMTE website and have supplied your email address, AMTE may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with AMTE and our services. We primarily use our website to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. AMTE takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.
Cookies
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. AMTE uses cookies to help AMTE identify and track visitors, their usage of AMTE website, and their website access preferences. AMTE visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using AMTE's websites, with the drawback that certain features of AMTE websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.
Business Transfers
In the unlikely event that AMTE dissolves or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred if acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of AMTE may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.
Ads
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by AMTE and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.
Comments
Comments and other content submitted to our anti-spam service are not saved on our servers unless they were marked as false positives, in which case we store them long enough to use them to improve the service to avoid future false positives.
Privacy Policy Changes
Although most changes are likely to be minor, AMTE may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in AMTE's sole discretion. AMTE encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have an AMTE account, you should also check your profile's dashboard for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
Change log:
February 11, 2014 - iniitial posting of Privacy Policy (patterned after Automattic.com)
